http://www.laconiadailysun.com/site/privacy.html

Save
What follows is the online privacy policy for LaconiaDailySun.com, LACONIADAILYSUN.COM, which governs personal information gathered on our Internet website (www.LaconiaDailySun.com).LACONIADAILYSUN.COM's Online SecurityWhen you, the client, purchase a product from LACONIADAILYSUN.COM, your information is collected and maintained solely by LACONIADAILYSUN.COM. If data is collected and/or maintained by any company other than LACONIADAILYSUN.COM, we will tell you at the point of collection. If you do not want to share your information with that company, you can choose not to use that service. Physical, electronic, and managerial procedures have been employed to safeguard the security and integrity of personal information. LACONIADAILYSUN.COM encrypts billing information wherever LACONIADAILYSUN.COM requests it.Personal Information that LACONIADAILYSUN.COM Collects OnlineLACONIADAILYSUN.COM collects personal information online, including names, postal and e-mail addresses, phone and facsimile numbers, billing information, and complaint information.LACONIADAILYSUN.COM does not knowingly collect or maintain any personal information from children under the age of 13. In addition, no part of our website is designed with the purpose of attracting any person under age 13.How LACONIADAILYSUN.COM Uses Personal Information Collected OnlineLACONIADAILYSUN.COM does not rent, sell or share personal information about you with other people or nonaffiliated companies, unless otherwise requested by you. Unless you otherwise consent, LACONIADAILYSUN.COM will use your personal information only for the purpose for which it is submitted, such as to reply to your emails, handle your complaints, and process billing and business requests related to program participation.At certain points where personal information is collected on the LACONIADAILYSUN.COM website, there may be a box where you may indicate you would like to be on a mailing list to receive information about LACONIADAILYSUN.COM and /or LACONIADAILYSUN.COM services.LACONIADAILYSUN.COM may choose to release personal information if release is required by law (for example, a subpoena) or regulation or is requested by a government agency; or where LACONIADAILYSUN.COM records indicate a company may be engaged in fraudulent activity or other deceptive practices that a governmental agency should be made aware of.Computer Tracking and CookiesA cookie is a small amount of data that is sent to your browser from a Web server and stored on your computer's hard drive. LACONIADAILYSUN.COM may choose to collect anonymous information passively using cookies. A cookie will not allow a website to learn any personally identifiable information (such as your real name and address) that you have not otherwise disclosed.Cookies might allow LACONIADAILYSUN.COM to automatically remember your Web browser when you visit website. LACONIADAILYSUN.COM generally uses cookies to facilitate online purchases. LACONIADAILYSUN.COM also may use cookies to measure statistics such as audience size and traffic patterns. This information is only collected in aggregate form and will not be linked to your personally identifiable information.The use of cookies is an industry standard, and they are currently used on most major websites. It is possible to adjust your Web browser preferences to alert you when a cookie is sent to your hard drive, or to refuse cookies altogether. While LACONIADAILYSUN.COM does not require you to use cookies, there might be certain services that will not function properly if you set your browser to refuse all cookies.About Third Party AdvertisingWe may use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you use our Services. If so, a list of these ad serving companies will be available here. These companies may use information (generally, not including your name, address, e-mail address or telephone number) about your visits to our sites or use of our Services and to other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. These companies may employ cookies and clear GIFs to measure advertising effectiveness. Any information that these third parties collect via cookies and clear GIFs is generally not personally identifiable (unless, for example, you provide personally identifiable information to them through an ad or e-mail message). We encourage you to read these businesses' privacy policies if you should have any concerns about how they will care for your personal information. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, see the Network Advertising Initiative's consumer website. Google Doubleclick for Publishers (DFP) is an ad network partner that displays ads on our Services. To improve your ad experience on our sites and Services and elsewhere on the Internet, we may send non-personal information to Google DFP based on your browser's activities, such as type of pages viewed and categories of interests, so that the advertising you see is relevant to you. Google DFP also may use information regarding its own users to select which ads to display. Click here to learn more about Google DFP's ad practices, including how to opt out of using anonymous information to select which ads to show you.Opt-Out of CookiesIf you wish to manage or opt-out of cookies utilized by our site and third party advertisers, you can take the following steps:You may be able to download an opt-out cookie from the third party advertiser's website allowing you to opt-out of cookies. Please visit the third party advertiser's websites for more information.Your web browser may allow you to manage what cookies are accepted or declined. These settings can usually be found in the preferences or options menus of your web browser.Your web browser may also allow you to manually view cookies and delete the cookies you don't want or need. Check your web browser's settings for more information.Websites that require registration may allow you to opt-out of cookies. Check the account settings or preferences section of the website for more information.For more information, please visit http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/.Problems or Complaints with the LACONIADAILYSUN.COM Privacy PolicyIf you have a complaint about LACONIADAILYSUN.COM compliance with this privacy policy, you may contact us at Admin@LaconiaDailySun.com.Conditions of UseLaconiaDailySun.com provides its services to you subject to the following conditions. If you visit or shop at LaconiaDailySun.com, you accept these conditions. Please read them carefully.PRIVACYPlease review our Privacy Policy, which also governs your visit to LaconiaDailySun.com, to understand our practices.ELECTRONIC COMMUNICATIONSWhen you visit LaconiaDailySun.com or send e-mails to us, you are communicating with us electronically. You consent to receive communications from us electronically. We will communicate with you by e-mail or by posting notices on this site. You agree that all agreements, notices, disclosures and other communications that we provide to you electronically satisfy any legal requirement that such communications be in writing.COPYRIGHTAll content included on this site, such as text, graphics, logos, button icons, images, audio clips, digital downloads, data compilations and software, is the property of LaconiaDailySun.com and is protected by United States and international copyright laws. The compilation of all content on this site is the exclusive property of LaconiaDailySun.com and protected by U.S. and international copyright laws. All software used on this site is the property of LaconiaDailySun.com and is protected by United States and international copyright laws.YOUR ACCOUNTIf you use this site, you are responsible for maintaining the confidentiality of your account and password and for restricting access to your computer, and you agree to accept responsibility for all activities that occur under your account or password. LaconiaDailySun.com does sell products for children, but it sells them to adults, who can purchase with a credit card. If you are under 18, you may use LaconiaDailySun.com only with involvement of a parent or guardian. LaconiaDailySun.com reserves the right to refuse service, terminate accounts, remove or edit content, or cancel orders in its sole discretion.SECURITYSecure Socket Layer (SSL) LaconiaDailySun.com uses SSL (Secure Socket Layer) encryption when transmitting certain kinds of information, such as financial services information or payment information. An icon resembling a padlock is displayed on the bottom of most browsers window during SSL transactions that involve credit cards and other forms of payment.Any time LaconiaDailySun.com asks you for a credit card number on LaconiaDailySun.com for payment or for verification purposes, it will be SSL encrypted. The information you provide will be stored securely on our servers. Once you choose to store or enter your credit card number on LaconiaDailySun.com, it will not be displayed back to you in its entirety when you retrieve or edit it in the future. Instead of the entire number, you will only see asterisks and either the first four digits or the last four digits of your number.
© Copyright 2020 The Laconia Daily Sun, 781 Union Ave. Laconia, NH | Terms of Use | Privacy Policy
Powered by BLOX Content Management System from TownNews.com.
Notifications
Settings
You don't have any notifications.
Get up-to-the-minute news sent straight to your device.
Topics
